(Leonard:)I didn't want you ending up
with a bad grade and get discouraged...
(Leonard:)...and give up on the idea
of going back to school.
(Penny:)Right, because me being in school
is so important to you.
(Penny:)That way, you wouldn't have to be dating
someone who's only a waitress.
(Leonard:)Come on, you know that's not true.
(Penny:)Do I? Listen to me.
I need to do this on my own.
(Penny:)If I fail, I fail. If I pass, I pass.
Do you get it?
- I'm sorry, I was just trying to help.
- Yeah, well, next time, don't.
(Penny:)Oh. And since you like stories so much...
(Penny:)...this is not the shoemaker
and the elves, okay?
This is give a man a fish, he eats it.
Teach a man to fish,
he sells it or something.
Whatever, I don't know. It's just
a lot better than what you did, you big jerk!
- You ever hear back from Hawking?
- No.
(Sheldon:)It would appear as if I've lost him.
(Sheldon:)Stupid brain.
- It'll be okay.
- How can it be okay?
(Sheldon:)Stephen Hawking's a genius
and he talks like a robot.